https://www.mbaexchange.com/privacy-policy/

Our Affiliations
Why a Top MBA?
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your trust and confidence are very important to us. To ensure and protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices.
The Information We CollectThis notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages, you can make requests and register to receive information. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
NameAddressEmail addressPhone numberProfessional profileAcademic profileActivities profile
The Way We Use InformationWe use the information you provide only to provide other information that is beneficial to you. We do not disclose or share this information with any outside parties. We use only non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website. We never use or share personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described on this website without also providing you a prior opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment to Data SecurityTo prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take all reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting any access or making corrections.
Contact UsShould you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us.
Why a Top MBA?
Privacy Policy
Services
Admissions Consulting
MBA (Full- or Part-time)
Executive MBA
Law School (JD)
Why Choose Us?
MBA (Full- or Part-time)
Executive MBA
Law School (JD)
